// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
      question: "This is also known as the author, creator, or producer of a message",
      answer: "Communicator",
      options: [
        "Communicator",
        "Message",
        "Audience",
        "Context",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
      question: "Refers to the idea expressing layers of meanings from the communicator. It can be real or imaginary",
      answer: "Message",
      options: [
        "Communicator",
        "Message",
        "Audience",
        "Context",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
      question: "Refers to a person, group, or organization to whom the message is either addressed, invoked or from whome feedback is expected",
      answer: "Audience",
      options: [
        "Communicator",
        "Message",
        "Audience",
        "Context",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
      question: "Refers to the time and place of communication, together with the conditions from the physical environment",
      answer: "Context",
      options: [
        "Communicator",
        "Message",
        "Audience",
        "Context",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
      question: "It is to explain, to describe, to entertain, and to persuade",
      answer: "Purpose",
      options: [
        "Exigency",
        "Medium",
        "Modality",
        "Purpose",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
      question: "Refers to the senses involved in decoding messages",
      answer: "Modality",
      options: [
        "Exigency",
        "Medium",
        "Modality",
        "Purpose",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
      question: "Is the technical means by which messages are communicated",
      answer: "Medium",
      options: [
        "Exigency",
        "Medium",
        "Modality",
        "Purpose",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
      question: "Refers to needs and situations that cause the production of video materials",
      answer: "Exigency",
      options: [
        "Exigency",
        "Medium",
        "Modality",
        "Purpose",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
      question: "Refers to the method of distributing the message as in print for newspaper, broadcast for radio and TV programs, and digital for movies",
      answer: "Circulation",
      options: [
        "Genre",
        "Circulation",
        "Movie",
        "Television program",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
      question: "Is the other term for class or category in which the viewing material belongs",
      answer: "Genre",
      options: [
        "Genre",
        "Circulation",
        "Movie",
        "Television program",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
      question: "Is a scheduled show broadcast through TV. It can be watched on cell phone or online",
      answer: "Television program",
      options: [
        "Genre",
        "Circulation",
        "Movie",
        "Television program",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
      question: "Is a film shown in a theater, on television, or on the Net",
      answer: "Movie",
      options: [
        "Genre",
        "Circulation",
        "Movie",
        "Television program",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
      question: "A genre of fiction set basically in the period from the 1850s to the end of 19th century in the Western United States",
      answer: "Western",
      options: [
        "Romance",
        "Thriller",
        "Western",
        "Horror",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
      question: "A classification of fiction that alludes to any talk or work commonly proposed to be humorous or interesting by inducing laughter",
      answer: "Comedy",
      options: [
        "Comedy",
        "Action",
        "Crime",
        "Animation",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
      question: "This type of Commercial is used to launch, update, or relaunch a product",
      answer: "Informative",
      options: [
        "Reminder",
        "Persuasive",
        "Informative",
        "Commercial",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
      question: "This type of Commercial is used to increase the demand for the product by comparing it with similar products and highlighting its best features",
      answer: "Persuasive",
      options: [
        "Reminder",
        "Persuasive",
        "Informative",
        "Commercial",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
      question: "This type of Commercial is used to reinforce previous promotional information",
      answer: "Reminder",
      options: [
        "Reminder",
        "Persuasive",
        "Informative",
        "Commercial",
    ]
  },
{
    numb: 18,
      question: "This type of music video shows an artist or band performing their song",
      answer: "Performance music video",
      options: [
        "Performance music video",
        "Concept-based music video",
        "Narrative music video",
        "Music Video",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
      question: "This type of music video contains dramatization of a story featured in the lyrics",
      answer: "Narrative music video",
      options: [
        "Performance music video",
        "Concept-based music video",
        "Narrative music video",
        "Music Video",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
      question: "This type of music video revolves around the concept or theme derived from the lyrics of the song",
      answer: "Concept-based music video",
      options: [
        "Performance music video",
        "Concept-based music video",
        "Narrative music video",
        "Music Video",
    ]
  },

  // you can make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];